var questionAnswer = [{
        "question": "I forgot my username, how do I sign in?",
        "answer": "Try using your email to login. Check out our tutorial videos for help, for more information",
        "link": "https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCBS7FryGH__DM5dfk1VaRvA"
    }, {
        "question": "I am trying to login, but my email is not verified, what do I do?",
        "answer": "Check your email for the verification link to validate it. However, you should still be able to login with your username. Check out our tutorial videos for more help",
        "link": "https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCBS7FryGH__DM5dfk1VaRvA"
    }, {
        "question": "I didn’t receive a verification code?",
        "answer": "If it is not in your email, request a new verification code to be sent. Check out our tutorial videos for help",
        "link": "https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCBS7FryGH__DM5dfk1VaRvA"
    }, {
        "question": "When signing in, it is asking me to login using a different method: Facebook, Gmail or LinkedIn?",
        "answer": "It means that you have used this email before, so it is now associated with that original account. Retry under the correct login method.",
        "link": ""
    }, {
        "question": "What is SpotJobs?",
        "answer": "SpotJobs is a platform which offers paid services between individuals. It allows people to earn extra money on a flexible schedule, and helps users get tasks done on a predefined budget by providing access to a wide database of qualified and affordable freelancers. Check out our videos for more details",
        "link": "https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCBS7FryGH__DM5dfk1VaRvA"
    }, {
        "question": "How do I contact SpotJobs?",
        "answer": "You can contact us at support@spotjobsapp.com",
        "link": ""
    }, {
        "question": "How do I contact SpotGigs?",
        "answer": "You can contact us at support@spotjobsapp.com",
        "link": ""
    }, {
        "question": "How do I post a job?",
        "answer": "Click on the section “Post a Job”, you can also use the green bubble on the website to create a job post. Posting a job is free for all users. For more information check out our tutorial videos",
        "link": "https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCBS7FryGH__DM5dfk1VaRvA"
    }, {
        "question": "What is SpotGigs?",
        "answer": "SpotGigs and SpotJobs are one platform, SpotGigs is the other name for SpotJobs.",
        "link": ""
    }, {
        "question": "Why am I not able to change my email?",
        "answer": "Only users who do not use social media accounts (Facebook, Gmail or LinkedIn) to sign in, can change their email or password. The new email will be activated only once you have validated it by clicking on the confirmation link sent to that email.",
        "link": ""
    }, {
        "question": "Why am I not able to change my password?",
        "answer": "Only users who do not use social media accounts to sign in (Facebook, Gmail or LinkedIn), can change their email or password. Go to your User Profile to change your email, and to the Setting section of the app or website to change your password.",
        "link": ""
    }, {
        "question": "Is Spotjobs free?",
        "answer": "Spotjobs is free to use, users have access to all features at no cost. However, premium members have access to more features and options.",
        "link": ""
    }, {
        "question": "What do premium members get?",
        "answer": "Premium members are able to add more pictures and videos. They also get an extra 30 minutes of tracking available after the appointment time has passed.",
        "link": ""
    }, {
        "question": "When do points expire?",
        "answer": "Points purchased are good for 12 months, and points earned by viewing ads expire after 6 months.",
        "link": ""
    }, {
        "question": "How do I become a premium member?",
        "answer": "You have few options, either click and view ads to earn and accumulate the points needed for the premium membership, or buy them. Check the “Subscription” section for membership options and for purchasing extra points. Note that points are earned only in the app.",
        "link": ""
    }, {
        "question": "Is SpotJobs available in my area?",
        "answer": "SpotJobs is available everywhere in the world. However, some regions will likely have a limited number of jobs or service providers if they are not enough users within that area. Join today and tell your friends about us.",
        "link": ""
    }, {
        "question": "Can I post jobs and offer my service as a freelancer too?",
        "answer": "Every user can be both a service provider and/or an employer.",
        "link": ""
    }, {
        "question": "Who can hire service provider",
        "answer": "Every user can be both a service provider and/or an employer.",
        "link": ""
    }, {
        "question": "Can service providers post jobs?",
        "answer": "With SpotJobs all users can post jobs, even if they are service providers.",
        "link": ""
    }, {
        "question": "Who can post a job?",
        "answer": "With SpotJobs all users can post jobs, even if they are service providers.",
        "link": ""
    }, {
        "question": "Who can become a service provider?",
        "answer": "Anyone with a knowhow, willing and able to work, can become a service provider.",
        "link": ""
    }, {
        "question": "Can I apply for jobs in different cities or countries?",
        "answer": "Service providers are able to apply for jobs anywhere in the world. Users can earn money even if they are traveling.",
        "link": ""
    }, {
        "question": "Can I post a job in a different city or country?",
        "answer": "Users can post jobs anywhere in the world, just remember to enter the correct address including city and country, when creating the post.",
        "link": ""
    }, {
        "question": "How do I earn free points to get free premium membership?",
        "answer": "Free points can be earned by clicking and viewing ads in the app. When accumulating enough you will be able to redeem them for a monthly or yearly membership.",
        "link": ""
    }, {
        "question": "what are points for?",
        "answer": "Free points can be earned by clicking and viewing ads in the app. When accumulating enough you will be able to redeem them for a monthly or yearly membership.",
        "link": ""
    }, {
        "question": "How do I earn points?",
        "answer": "Free points can be earned by clicking and viewing ads in the app. When accumulating enough you will be able to redeem them for a monthly or yearly membership.",
        "link": ""
    }, {
        "question": "I am few points short to have enough for a monthly/ yearly membership, can I buy the extra points needed?",
        "answer": "Users can purchase as many points as needed in the “Subscription” section of the app and website.",
        "link": ""
    }, {
        "question": "Where and how do I buy points?",
        "answer": "Users can purchase as many points as needed in the “Subscription” section of the app and website.",
        "link": ""
    }, {
        "question": "How do service providers get paid?",
        "answer": "Payments for jobs are done ONLY via SpotJobs. Any payment and transactions done outside the platform will result in the immediate termination or suspension of the user’s account.",
        "link": ""
    }, {
        "question": "Can I get paid outside spotjobs?",
        "answer": "Payments for jobs are done ONLY via SpotJobs. Any payment and transactions done outside the platform will result in the immediate termination or suspension of the user’s account.",
        "link": ""
    }, {
        "question": "How do I unsubscribe from e-mails?",
        "answer": "You can unsubscribe by changing your setting in the “Setting” section.",
        "link": ""
    }, {
        "question": "Do you conduct background checks?",
        "answer": "We do not conduct background checks at this time. However, all users can apply to get their ID verified using AI technology to validate their account authenticity.",
        "link": ""
    }, {
        "question": "I get a message saying that my user profile is not complete, why?",
        "answer": "Check to see that all the sections under the “User Profile” are completed, that you have entered a complete address with a street number, have verified your email (only users not using Facebook, Gmail or LinkedIn need to get their email verified), and that you have accepted the Terms and Conditions… remember to SAVE your changes!",
        "link": ""
    }, {
        "question": "Do I have to enter an address?",
        "answer": "It is important to enter a full address to display your approximate geolocation, your profile will not be complete, and you will not be able to access any features until you do so. Furthermore, if you are going to be a service provider, prospect employers will not be able to see your profile under the section “Find Help” if you did not enter an address. Remember that the address in your user profile is not seen by other users.",
        "link": ""
    }, {
        "question": "I cannot find jobs or service providers near me?",
        "answer": "Did you check your user profile to make sure you have selected a Radius wide enough for your search? You can always widen your enquiry under the “Map View” section of “Find Help” and “Find Jobs,” or use the in-app filter. It is also possible that not many users are currently in your area. Help spread the word, and tell your friends about us.",
        "link": ""
    }, {
        "question": "What is the Radius for?",
        "answer": "The Radius setup in the user profile guides your search. When you look for jobs or for service providers, the result you will get are found within that radius. If you are a service provider, you will receive notifications for jobs matching your profile within that radius.",
        "link": ""
    }, {
        "question": "Is my address seen by other users?",
        "answer": "The address posted in your user profile is not seen by other users. However, when you post a job and provide an address there, it will be displayed to the service provider you will book the job with.",
        "link": ""
    }, {
        "question": "Is my personal information seen by other users?",
        "answer": "Personal information entered in the section User Profile is not shared with other users. However, when you post a job, or if you are a service provider and apply for a job, other users may see your first name, first initial of your last name and your profile picture. Your last name will be displayed only once you have been booked for a job.",
        "link": ""
    }, {
        "question": "Is my personal information safe?",
        "answer": "We take  the safety of your personal information very seriously, for that reason we encrypt all user data.",
        "link": ""
    }, {
        "question": "What is ID verification?",
        "answer": "All users can apply to have their Identity verified using a secure AI technology software to validate their account authenticity. The AI process involves verifying identity through selfies, government-issued ID card, driving license, or passport. The entire process takes approximatively 30 seconds on average. Being ID verified can help users get more jobs. Available in most countries around the world. A low processing fee applies.",
        "link": ""
    }, {
        "question": "Can I write a review about a user without joining SpotJobs?",
        "answer": "To write a review you need to have worked directly with that service provider or employer, and only through SpotJobs.",
        "link": ""
    }, {
        "question": "Who can write a review ?",
        "answer": "Users can post reviews about each other after completing a job.",
        "link": ""
    }, {
        "question": "Do you take a commission?",
        "answer": "Only employers pay a 15% service fee on jobs completed. The fee covers payment processing, administration cost and maintenance of the platform.",
        "link": ""
    }, {
        "question": "How do I withdraw my money, and what are the fees?",
        "answer": "To withdraw your transferable balance just click on the “Withdraw” button under the section “Payments & Transactions” in your User Profile. All withdraws are done via PayPal. In most cases, your payment transfers immediately. However, there are occasions when it may take up to 24 hours. If it has been more than 24 hours, please contact PayPal. You must use your own registered PayPal account. You should determine which type of PayPal account works for you. PayPal may limit your account functionality until you pass their verification procedures and they usually require a bank account or credit card. In addition to a small per-transfer fee SpotJobs may charge, there may be additional costs on PayPal's side. PayPal changes their minimum and maximum transaction amounts from time to time, and you should check with PayPal for current information. Typically, transactions have a minimum of $1.00 and a maximum of $10,000. PayPal's outgoing withdrawal fees vary by method, destination country, and currency choice (see PayPal's withdrawal fee calculator for details)( https://www.paypal.com/). PayPal also may charge additional fees based on your location. For example, PayPal India classifies transfers from SpotJobs as payments for services and charges additional fees.",
        "link": "https://www.paypal.com/in/webapps/mpp/paypal-fees"
    }, {
        "question": "How much does it cost to post a job?",
        "answer": "It is free to post a job, however we charge a service fee of 15% of the job budget to be collected in escrow when you book a job. If a job is cancelled the service fee is returned.",
        "link": ""
    }, {
        "question": "Can I pay outside SpotJobs?",
        "answer": "Payment are done exclusively via SpotJobs, any payment done and negotiated outside the platform will result in user account termination.",
        "link": ""
    }, {
        "question": "Can I pay without using spotjobs, or use a different payment method?",
        "answer": "Payment are done exclusively via SpotJobs, any payment done and negotiated outside the platform will result in user account termination.",
        "link": ""
    }, {
        "question": "What are Escrow services?",
        "answer": "SpotJobs provides escrow services to Users to deliver, hold, and/or receive payment for Jobs, and to pay fees to SpotJobs. For more details check the Terms & Conditions.",
        "link": ""
    }, {
        "question": "In case of a dispute what can I do?",
        "answer": "If users fail to come to a mutual resolution, SpotJobs provides a Dispute Assistance Program as a mechanism to resolve the Dispute. Dispute Assistance is only available via the app under the section My Jobs: Booked Job, where a Dispute button is located and available when applicable, and after funding are in Escrow for that job. Dispute Assistance is not available after the Dispute Assistance Deadline. The language accepted of the dispute assistance will be English only. Any false claim or misleading actions can result in an account deletion and ban from SpotJobs sites and services. For more details check the Terms & Conditions.",
        "link": ""
    }, {
        "question": "What to do if I have a problem?",
        "answer": "If users fail to come to a mutual resolution, SpotJobs provides a Dispute Assistance Program as a mechanism to resolve the Dispute. Dispute Assistance is only available via the app under the section My Jobs: Booked Job, where a Dispute button is located and available when applicable, and after funding are in Escrow for that job. Dispute Assistance is not available after the Dispute Assistance Deadline. The language accepted of the dispute assistance will be English only. Any false claim or misleading actions can result in an account deletion and ban from SpotJobs sites and services. For more details check the Terms & Conditions.",
        "link": ""
    }, {
        "question": "Can SpotJobs revoke user access?",
        "answer": "SpotJobs may terminate user privileges immediately and without notice for any reason whatsoever. Upon such termination, you must immediately cease accessing or using the Sites.",
        "link": ""
    }, {
        "question": "Can you delete my account? Can you revoke my account access ? can you cancel my account?",
        "answer": "SpotJobs may terminate user privileges immediately and without notice for any reason whatsoever. Upon such termination, you must immediately cease accessing or using the Sites.",
        "link": ""
    }, {
        "question": "Can you delete my account?",
        "answer": "SpotJobs may terminate user privileges immediately and without notice for any reason whatsoever. Upon such termination, you must immediately cease accessing or using the Sites.",
        "link": ""
    }, {
        "question": "Can you revoke my account access ?",
        "answer": "SpotJobs may terminate user privileges immediately and without notice for any reason whatsoever. Upon such termination, you must immediately cease accessing or using the Sites.",
        "link": ""
    }, {
        "question": "can you cancel my account?",
        "answer": "SpotJobs may terminate user privileges immediately and without notice for any reason whatsoever. Upon such termination, you must immediately cease accessing or using the Sites.",
        "link": ""
    }, {
        "question": "Can I change the default language?",
        "answer": "SpotJobs offers its platform in several languages. However, SpotJobs’ official language of communication is English. All communications including disputes need to be submitted in English only, if any communication is sent in any other languages it will be disregarded.",
        "link": ""
    }, {
        "question": "Do users pay taxes?",
        "answer": "SpotJobs may be required by applicable law to collect taxes or levies including, without limitation, withholding income tax or VAT (while some countries may refer to VAT using other terms, e.g. GST, we’ll just refer to VAT, GST and any local sales taxes collectively as “VAT”) in the jurisdiction of the Service provider (the 'Taxes'). In such instances, any amounts SpotJobs is required to collect or withhold for the payment of any such Taxes shall be collected in addition to the fees owed to SpotJobs under the Terms of Services.",
        "link": ""
    }, {
        "question": "Do I pay tax?",
        "answer": "SpotJobs may be required by applicable law to collect taxes or levies including, without limitation, withholding income tax or VAT (while some countries may refer to VAT using other terms, e.g. GST, we’ll just refer to VAT, GST and any local sales taxes collectively as “VAT”) in the jurisdiction of the Service provider (the 'Taxes'). In such instances, any amounts SpotJobs is required to collect or withhold for the payment of any such Taxes shall be collected in addition to the fees owed to SpotJobs under the Terms of Services.",
        "link": ""
    }, {
        "question": "When do I get paid?",
        "answer": "When a booked job has been completed, the Employer needs to click on the button “Mark Job As Done” to release the funds to the service provider. ",		
        "link": ""
    }, {
        "question": "Do I get my money back if I cancel a job?",
        "answer": "If the Employer wants to cancel a job with funds held in escrow, he must click “Cancel The Job”, and will get refunded up to the scheduled appointment day and time for that job. If the Service Provider does not show to the job’s appointment, the Employer can also cancel the job by clicking “Cancel The Job” and check the box for NO SHOW, the Employer will then get refunded within 24h.  Users can contact Dispute Assistance if they have any concerns, Dispute Assistance is only available via the app under the section My Jobs: Booked Job, where a Dispute button is located and available when applicable, and after funding are in Escrow for that job. Any false claim or misleading actions can result in an account deletion and ban from SpotJobs sites and services.",
        "link": ""
    }, {
        "question": "Can my account be deleted by SpotJobs?",
        "answer": "SpotJobs may terminate users’ privilege to use or access the Sites and Services immediately and without notice for any reason whatsoever. Any false claim or misleading actions can result in an account deletion and ban from SpotJobs sites and services.",
        "link": ""
    }, {
        "question": "How do I delete my account?",
        "answer": "The “Delete my account” section can be found under “Setting.”",
        "link": ""
    }, {
        "question": "Why am I not able to see the full job details?",
        "answer": "If you are looking at the jobs via the category filter on the website’s landing page, you will be able to see only the pucks. You need to sign in to see the job details.",
        "link": ""
    }, {
        "question": "Why can I not apply for jobs?",
        "answer": "Only service providers can apply for jobs. You can change your user status under the section User Profile to become a service provider. Remember to save your changes.",
        "link": ""
    }, {
        "question": "How do I turn off notifications?",
        "answer": "You can turn off your notifications in the “Setting” section of the website or app. Other options are also available, such as turning off your account making you temporarily invisible to other users.",
        "link": ""
    }, {
        "question": "When is tracking available?",
        "answer": "Tracking is available 30 minutes before the appointment time. Employers will be able to see the freelancer’s trip to the job’s address location. However, in order for tracking to be activated the Service provider will have to open the app to provide his geolocation. Premium members can also track the Service providers up to 30 minutes after the appointment time.",
        "link": ""
    }, {
        "question": "I am in the Tracking section, why can I not see the service provider?",
        "answer": "Tracking starts only 30 minutes before the appointment time. However, in order for tracking to be activated the service provider has to open the app to give his geolocation. Premium members can also track service providers up to 30 minutes after the appointment time.",
        "link": ""
    }, {
        "question": "How do I chat with a user?",
        "answer": "Chats are available only once users have both accepted a job offer, and until the job is completed or closed. A chat bubble will appear under the user profile, just click on it to start chatting. Users will be able to send text and voice messages.",
        "link": ""
    }, {
        "question": "I closed my job by accident, can I get my money back?",
        "answer": "When you “Mark a job as done”  SpotJobs releases the funds to the Service Provider, therefore once that action is completed, those funds cannot be refundable by SpotJobs. You could always ask your Service Provider to refund you via a job created just for that purpose.",
        "link": ""
    }, {
        "question": "Can I refund my employer for a job I did?",
        "answer": "Service Providers are not able to refund directly any payment via SpotJobs. However, users always have the option to pay each other via jobs.",
        "link": ""
    }, {
        "question": "A job I worked was marked as canceled even though I completed the job, so I did not get paid, what can I do?",
        "answer": "Users can contact Dispute Assistance if they have any concerns, Dispute Assistance is only available via the app under the section My Jobs: Booked Job, where a Dispute button is located and available when applicable, and after funding are in Escrow for that job. Any false claim or misleading actions can result in an account deletion and ban from SpotJobs sites and services. ",
        "link": ""
    }, {
        "question": "How do I make sure I will get paid by the employer?",
        "answer": "It is important that the Service Provider and the Employer click on the button “Starting The Job” (under the section My jobs: Booked jobs) before the Service Provider actually starts working, you also need to make sure the employer clicks on “Mark Job As Done” (under the section My jobs: Booked jobs) before you leave the job site, to insure that the funds are released to you after you have completed the job. SpotJobs reserves the right to ban any dishonest users.",
        "link": ""
    }, {
        "question": "What if users forget to take action on a booked job after the appointment has past?",
        "answer": "If a booked job has no activity, that means no user has marked the job as started, completed or cancelled, in which case 24 hours after the appointment date has passed, it will be cancelled and the funds will be returned to the employer.",
        "link": ""
    }, {
        "question": "What is the minimum budget allowed?",
        "answer": "The minimum budget allowed is $10.00.",
        "link": ""
    }, {
        "question": "How do I become a service provider?",
        "answer": "Under your User Profile, you have the option to become a Service Provider, when you do so just fill out the remaining sections and remember to save your changes. Check out our tutorial videos for help, for more information",
        "link": "https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCBS7FryGH__DM5dfk1VaRvA"
    }

];
